□When Posting to Leafnote
・Posted Flipnotes will be uploaded to Leafnote on the Nintendo DSi. 
・Uploaded Flipnotes will be published on the internet, allowing other users to view and download them. Other users may also reproduce, alter and/or modify the Flipnotes. Only Flipnotes that are locked at the time of posting cannot be altered or modified. Do not upload any Flipnotes that may be illegal, harmful or may violate any third party rights such as portrait rights, privacy rights or copyrights. In particular, if you upload and/or change photos displaying people, ensure to obtain their permission beforehand.
・Posted Flipnotes may be used by third parties for other purposes.
・Flipnotes posted to Leafnote can be deleted from the Nintendo DSi system on which they were created. However, Flipnotes posted by third parties by revising or reposting the original Flipnote cannot be deleted.
 ・When you post a Flipnote, the user name on your Nintendo DSi system will also be posted. For information on changing your user name, refer to the Profile section of the Nintendo DSi Operations Manual. Please be sure not to include personal information in your user name, as it will be visible to third parties.
・Please do not post any material that infringes on the rights of others (such as copyrights, portrait rights or privacy rights), contains personal information, is illegal, harmful or violates the Terms of Use.
・Posted Flipnotes may be removed in accordance with the Terms of Use at any time and without notice.